[[road shimmer
wiggling the vision
heat heat waves
i’m swimming in a mirror]]
sometimes, all i think about is you
late nights in the middle of june
heat waves been faking me out
can’t make you happier now
usually i put
something on tv
so we never think
about you and me
but today i see
our reflections
clearly in hollywood
laying on the screen
you just need a better life than this
you need something I can never give
fake water all across the road
it’s gone now the night has come but
sometimes, all i think about is you
late nights in the middle of june
heat waves been faking me out
can’t make you happier now
you can’t fight it
you can’t breathe
you say something so loving but
now I’ve got to let you go
you’ll be better off in someone new
i don’t wanna be alone
you know it hurts me too
you look so broken when you cry
one more and then i’ll say goodbye
sometimes, all i think about is you
late nights in the middle of june
heat waves been faking me out
can’t make you happier now
i just wonder what you’re dreaming of
when you sleep and smile so comfortable
i just wish that I could give you that
that look that’s perfectly un-sad
sometimes, all i think about is you
late nights in the middle of june
heat waves been faking me out
sometimes, all i think about is you
late nights in the middle of june
heat waves been faking me out
can’t make you happier now